Register of the Robert Charles Hill papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to Spain File, 1962-1972
  - Correspondence, 1969-1972
    - Martin, Graham A., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 49)
    - Martin, John Bartlow, 1969 (Box-folder 151: 50)
    - Martin, Vernon P., undated (Box-folder 151: 51)
    - Martin Gamero, Amalia, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 52)
    - Martin Villa, Rodolfo, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 53)
    - Martinell, Rafael Maria, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 54)
    - Martinez Bordiu, Andres, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 55)
    - Martinez Bordiu, Carmen, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 56)
    - Martinez Bordiu, Cristobal, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 57)
    - Martinez de Galinsoga y Ros, Francisco, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 58)
    - Martinez Villa, Luis, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 59)
    - Marvin, Langdon P., Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 60)
    - Mason, Mrs. Dandridge K., 1971 (Box-folder 151: 61)
    - Mason, Elizabeth B., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 151: 62)
    - Mason, Joseph A., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 63)
    - Mason, W. Beverley, Jr., 1969 (Box-folder 151: 64)
    - Mathies, Salvador, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 65)
    - Matthes, R., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 66)
    - Mayer, Robert E., 1971 (Box-folder 151: 67)
    - Maynard, Dale W., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 68)
    - Mead, Edgar T., Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 69)
    - Medina Gamero, Manuel, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 70)
    - Melady, Thomas Patrick, 1971 (Box-folder 151: 71)
    - Melia Sinisterra, Jose, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 72)
    - Mellor, John E., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 151: 73)
    - Melvin, Frances C., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 74)
    - Merck, Albert W., 1969 (Box-folder 151: 75)
    - Merry del Val, Marquis of, 1969 (Box-folder 151: 76)
    - Mesdag, J. V., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 77)
    - Meyer, Charles A., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 151: 78)
    - Meyer, Frank G., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 79)
    - Meyer, John C., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 151: 80)
    - Meyer, John M., Jr., 1969 (Box-folder 151: 81)
    - Meyers, Albert H., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 82)
    - Michener, James A., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 151: 83)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II, 1969 (Box-folder 151: 84)
    - Milans del Bosch, Gonzalo, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 85)
    - Milburn, Edward M., 1971 (Box-folder 151: 86)
    - Milks, Harold K., 1969 (Box-folder 151: 87)
    - Miller, G. William, 1971 (Box-folder 151: 88)
    - Miller, George P., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 89)
    - Miller, H. R., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 90)
    - Miller, Joe D., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 91)
    - Miller, Raymond W., 1969 (Box-folder 151: 92)
    - Miller, S. S., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 93)
    - Miller, Victor, 1971 (Box-folder 151: 94)
    - Miller, William M., 1970 (Box-folder 151: 95)
    - Milliken, Roger, undated (Box-folder 151: 96)
    - Minotto, James, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 151: 97)
    - Minovich, Jack, 1969 (Box-folder 151: 98)
    - Mitchell, David, 1970 (Box-folder 151: 99)
    - Mitchell, John N., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 151: 100)
    - Mitchell, Matthew J., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 151: 101)
    - Moats, Sanford K., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 152: 1)
    - Mobley, E. L., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 2)
    - Moehlman, Arthur H., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 3)
    - Mohr, Jack, 1969 (Box-folder 152: 4)
    - Molina Orta, Federico, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 5)
    - Molinary Matias, Ramon Dario, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 152: 6)
    - Mollenhoff, Clark R., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 152: 7)
    - Mollohan, Robert H., 1971 (Box-folder 152: 8)
    - Monagan, John S., 1969 (Box-folder 152: 9)
    - Mondejar, Marques de, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 152: 10)
    - Monk, Peter K., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 11)
    - Monreal Luque, Alberto, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 12)
    - Monroe, Frank A., Jr., 1969 (Box-folder 152: 13)
    - Montemayor, Ernest A., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 14)
    - Monterey Railway, Light and Power Company, 1971 (Box-folder 152: 15)
    - Montero Mateo, Alfonso, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 16)
    - Montgomery, Joseph West, Jr., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 152: 17)
    - Montllor, Ellen A., undated (Box-folder 152: 18)
    - Moor, Edgar J., 1969 (Box-folder 152: 19)
    - Moore, George S., 1971 (Box-folder 152: 20)
    - Moore, John D. J., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 152: 21)
    - Moore, Jonathan, 1971 (Box-folder 152: 22)
    - Moore, Steven, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 23)
    - Moore, T. Holmes, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 152: 24)
    - Moorer, T. H., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 152: 25)
    - Moorman, Lewis J., Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 26)
    - Moquin, George A., 1971 (Box-folder 152: 27)
    - Morales Gomez Caminero, Pedro, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 28)
    - Moran, Marcelino, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 29)
    - Moreno, Mario, 1969 (Box-folder 152: 30)
    - Morey, Florence, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 152: 31)
    - Morgan, Carroll, 1969 (Box-folder 152: 32)
    - Morgan, Neil, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 152: 33)
    - Morgan, Thomas E., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 34)
    - Morris, Robert, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 152: 35)
    - Morrissey, Carol A., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 152: 36)
    - Morrow, Wright, 1969 (Box-folder 152: 37)
    - Morse, F. Bradford, 1971 (Box-folder 152: 38)
    - Morse, John H., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 39)
    - Mortes Alfonso, Vicente, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 40)
    - Morton, Roald A., 1971 (Box-folder 152: 41)
    - Morton, Rogers C. B., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 152: 42)
    - Morton, Thruston B., 1969 (Box-folder 152: 43)
    - Mosbacher, Emil, Jr., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 152: 44)
    - Moscoso, Guillermo, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 45)
    - Moss, Ambler H., Jr., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 152: 46)
    - Motrico, Conde de, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 47)
    - Mowrer, Richard, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 152: 48)
    - Muchada y Paraire, Damian, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 49)
    - Muller, Cathey, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 152: 50)
    - Muls, R. L., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 51)
    - Mulvaney, James F., 1971 (Box-folder 152: 52)
    - Mundt, Mary E., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 152: 53)
    - Munoz, Antonio, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 54)
    - Munoz Grandes, Agustin, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 55)
    - Munro, George F., 1969 (Box-folder 152: 56)
    - Muriel de los Rios, Jose Luis, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 57)
    - Murphy, James Lawrence, 1969 (Box-folder 152: 58)
    - Murphy, Robert D., 1969 (Box-folder 152: 59)
    - Murphy, W. B., 1969 (Box-folder 152: 60)
    - Muse, Martha T., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 61)
    - Mussman, Mack M., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 152: 62)
    - Muzzy, Richard D., 1969 (Box-folder 152: 63)
    - Nabuco, Mauricio, 1971 (Box-folder 152: 64)
    - Navarro Garnica, Luis, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 65)
    - Neal, Jack D., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 152: 66)
    - Needleman, Lucy R., 1971 (Box-folder 152: 67)
    - Negri, Ralph, 1969 (Box-folder 152: 68)
    - Neil, Mary, 1969 (Box-folder 152: 69)
    - Nelson, Clifford C., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 70)
    - Nelson, Richard E., Jr., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 152: 71)
    - Nelthorpe, Clive R., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 72)
    - Newberry, Daniel O., 1971 (Box-folder 152: 73)
    - Ney, R. B., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 74)
    - Nichols, Bill, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 75)
    - Nichols, Louis B., 1969 (Box-folder 152: 76)
    - Nicola, Ion, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 152: 77)
    - Nieto, Alfonso, 1970 (Box-folder 152: 78)
    - Nitche, William W., 1970 (Box-folder 152: 79)
    - Nixon, F. Donald, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 152: 80)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 152: 81)
    - Noakes, Frank L., 1969 (Box-folder 152: 82)
    - Norton, W. Josiah, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 153: 1)
    - Nunez, Julio E., 1970 (Box-folder 153: 2)
    - Nunez Portuondo, Emilio, 1969 (Box-folder 153: 3)
    - Nutter, G. Warren, 1971 (Box-folder 153: 4)
    - Nyaradi, Nicholas, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 153: 5)
    - Nyary, Nicholas, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 6)
    - O'Bolger, Diego, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 153: 7)
    - O'Connor, Jean C., 1971 (Box-folder 153: 8)
    - O'Connor, Roderic L., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 153: 9)
    - Odriozola, Teresa de, 1971 (Box-folder 153: 10)
    - Oehlert, Benjamin H., Jr., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 153: 11)
    - Ohmans, John L., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 153: 12)
    - Okie, John B., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 153: 13)
    - Olds, Glenn A., 1971 (Box-folder 153: 14)
    - Olmedo del Castillo, Maia del Carmen, 1971 (Box-folder 153: 15)
    - Olson, V. Edward, 1971 (Box-folder 153: 16)
    - Oltra Molto, Enrique, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 17)
    - Onate, Virgilio, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 18)
    - Ordonez, Antonio, 1971 (Box-folder 153: 19)
    - Ordway, John, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 153: 20)
    - O'Reilly, Marquesa de, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 21)
    - Oriol y Urquijo, Antonio Maria de, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 22)
    - Ortega, Alberto, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 153: 23)
    - Ortega, Milagros, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 24)
    - Ortiz, Frank V., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 153: 25)
    - Ortiz Mena, Antonio, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 26)
    - Ortiz Monasterio, Juan M. O., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 153: 27)
    - Osborne, Stanley de J., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 153: 28)
    - O'Sullivan, Declan, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 29)
    - O'Sullivan, Terry, 1971 (Box-folder 153: 30)
    - Oswald, Victor M., 1970 (Box-folder 153: 31)
    - Otero Navascues, Jose Marie, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 32)
    - Oulahan, Richard, 1969 (Box-folder 153: 33)
    - Ozark, Stanley W., 1969 (Box-folder 153: 34)
    - Padilla Nervo, Luis, 1971 (Box-folder 153: 35)
    - Page, John H., 1969 (Box-folder 153: 36)
    - Page, Raymond S., Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 153: 37)
    - Paine, John Paul, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 153: 38)
    - Palenzuela, Ray, 1969 (Box-folder 153: 39)
    - Pallas, Jorge, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 40)
    - Palmby, Clarence D., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 153: 41)
    - Palmer, Bruce, Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 153: 42)
    - Palmer, C. English, 1971 (Box-folder 153: 43)
    - Palmer, F. F., 1970 (Box-folder 153: 44)
    - Palmer, Robert B., 1970 (Box-folder 153: 45)
    - Parker, Albert L., 1969 (Box-folder 153: 46)
    - Parker, Peg, undated (Box-folder 153: 47)
    - Parker, Mrs. Stanley B., 1969 (Box-folder 153: 48)
    - Parlade, Enrique, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 49)
    - Parsons, Givon, 1969 (Box-folder 153: 50)
    - Parsons, Irene, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 51)
    - Parsons, J. Graham, 1969 (Box-folder 153: 52)
    - Partridge, Daniel, III, 1969 (Box-folder 153: 53)
    - Pastor, Joseph, 1969 (Box-folder 153: 54)
    - Patman, Wright, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 55)
    - Patton, Stuart W., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 153: 56)
    - Pavesio Zorita, Lorenzo, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 57)
    - Pawley, Eugene D., 1969 (Box-folder 153: 58)
    - Peale, Norman Vincent, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 59)
    - Pearson, R. J., Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 153: 60)
    - Peek, Scott I., 1969 (Box-folder 153: 61)
    - Pelaez, Miguel, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 62)
    - Pendleton, Morris B., 1970 (Box-folder 153: 63)
    - Pepper, Claude, 1970 (Box-folder 153: 64)
    - Peralta, Angel, 1971 (Box-folder 154: 1)
    - Percy, Charles H., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 2)
    - Pereyra y Peraza, Miguel, 1971 (Box-folder 154: 3)
    - Perez Cerda, Francisco, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 4)
    - Perez de Sevilla y Ayala, Fernando, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 5)
    - Perez Galan y Rebozo, Ignacio, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 6)
    - Perez Ochoa, Robert, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 154: 7)
    - Perez Vineta y Lucio, Alfonso, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 8)
    - Perez y Perez, Domingo, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 9)
    - Perkins, Helen, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 10)
    - Perkins, Mildred K., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 154: 11)
    - Perkins, Milo, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 12)
    - Perren, Dale R., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 13)
    - Peters, Philip G., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 14)
    - Peterson, Arthur L., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 15)
    - Peterson, Clifford C., 1971 (Box-folder 154: 16)
    - Peterson, Peter G., 1971 (Box-folder 154: 17)
    - Peterson, Val, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 18)
    - Peterson, Walter, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 19)
    - Petit Herrera, Luis Alberto, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 20)
    - Phelps, P. A., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 21)
    - Phifer, James H., Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 22)
    - Phillips, Howard, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 23)
    - Phillips, Randolph, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 24)
    - Phelger, Herman, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 25)
    - Pike, Gilbert P., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 26)
    - Pingree, Michael M., 1971 (Box-folder 154: 27)
    - Plaisted, Harris M., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 28)
    - Plaza, Galo, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 154: 29)
    - Pohl, Stanley H., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 30)
    - Polk, James H., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 31)
    - Polk, T. H., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 32)
    - Porges, John M., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 33)
    - Potsma, Joost, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 34)
    - Potts, Stephen D., 1971 (Box-folder 154: 35)
    - Powell, Peter W., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 36)
    - Powell, Wesley, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 37)
    - Prager, Herbert, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 154: 38)
    - Pratt, Page B., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 154: 39)
    - Pray, Malcolm S., Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 40)
    - Primo de Rivera, Pilar, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 41)
    - Pryor, Samuel F., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 42)
    - Puebla de Parga, Marques Ignacio de, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 43)
    - Puga, Carlos E., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 44)
    - Purnell, Thomas I., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 45)
    - Putnam, Paul, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 46)
    - Quackenbush, D. Van, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 47)
    - Quackenbush, Peter, 1971 (Box-folder 154: 48)
    - Quesada Porto, Fernando, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 49)
    - Quinn, Arthur L., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 154: 50)
    - Quinonez, Margarita de, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 154: 51)
    - Rabb, Maxwell M., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 52)
    - Radewagen, Fred, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 154: 53)
    - Ramos, Richard, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 54)
    - Ramos Salido, Antonio, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 55)
    - Ramsey, Lewis A., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 56)
    - Rather, Mary, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 57)
    - Ravotto, Joseph D., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 154: 58)
    - Razquin Jene, Jose Maria, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 59)
    - Reagan, James R., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 60)
    - Real Sociedad Colombina Onubense, 1971 (Box-folder 154: 61)
    - Rebozo, C. G., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 154: 62)
    - Rebozo, I. P. G., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 63)
    - Rector, William G., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 64)
    - Redford, T. S., 1971 (Box-folder 154: 65)
    - Redo, Joaquin, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 154: 66)
    - Reid, Ogden, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 67)
    - Reifel, Ben, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 68)
    - Rein Segura, Carlos, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 69)
    - Reinhardt, G. Frederick, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 70)
    - Religiosas Oblatas, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 71)
    - Rey, Santiago, undated (Box-folder 154: 72)
    - Rhodes, John J., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 73)
    - Rhyne, Charles S., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 74)
    - Ribera, Andres, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 75)
    - Rice, Miriam, 1971 (Box-folder 154: 76)
    - Rich, Clyde K., 1971 (Box-folder 154: 77)
    - Richard, Joseph R., 1971 (Box-folder 154: 78)
    - Richardson, David C., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 154: 79)
    - Richardson, Elliot L., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 80)
    - Richardson, J. A. W., 1969 (Box-folder 154: 81)
    - Richardson, John, Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 82)
    - Richmond, Elsie, 1971 (Box-folder 154: 83)
    - Rickenbacker, Edward V., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 84)
    - Rielly, John E., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 85)
    - Riordan, Leo J., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 86)
    - Rishel, Andy L., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 87)
    - Rivas Micoud, Jose P., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 88)
    - Rivera, Rudolph L., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 89)
    - Rivero, Horacio, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 154: 90)
    - Rivers, L. Mendel, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 154: 91)
    - Rivers, Marion, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 92)
    - Roache, Charlotte, 1971 (Box-folder 154: 93)
    - Robles, Fernando, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 154: 94)
    - Robredo Soler, Alberto, 1970 (Box-folder 154: 95)
    - Rocheta, Manuel F., 1970 (Box-folder 154: 96)
    - Rockefeller, David, 1969 (Box-folder 154: 97)
    - Rockwell, Stuart W., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 154: 98)
    - Roddy, Kaye, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 1)
    - Roderick, George H., 1969 (Box-folder 155: 2)
    - Rodrigo, Joseph, 1969 (Box-folder 155: 3)
    - Rodriguez, Alberto, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 155: 4)
    - Rodriguez, Anastasia M. de, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 5)
    - Rodriguez, Esther, 1971 (Box-folder 155: 6)
    - Rodriguez, George H., 1971 (Box-folder 155: 7)
    - Rodriguez Bustelo de Alonso Vega, Ramona, 1971 (Box-folder 155: 8)
    - Rodriguez Laucirica, Jesus M., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 9)
    - Rodriguez Munoz, Julio, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 10)
    - Roe, Robert A., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 11)
    - Rogers, William P., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 155: 12)
    - Roll, Sylvester J., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 155: 13)
    - Romeral, Marquesa del, 1971 (Box-folder 155: 14)
    - Romero, Emilio, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 15)
    - Romero, Pepe, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 16)
    - Romero Manso, Juan, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 17)
    - Romney, George, 1971 (Box-folder 155: 18)
    - Roosevelt, Selwa, 1969 (Box-folder 155: 19)
    - Root, John F., 1971 (Box-folder 155: 20)
    - Rosaia, Helen C., 1971 (Box-folder 155: 21)
    - Rosal, Juan del, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 22)
    - Ross, Stanley, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 23)
    - Rossman, Guy C., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 24)
    - Rothschild, Louis S., 1971 (Box-folder 155: 25)
    - Rourke, Raymond A., 1969 (Box-folder 155: 26)
    - Rowe, David N., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 155: 27)
    - Rowe, James, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 155: 28)
    - Rowley, James J., 1971 (Box-folder 155: 29)
    - Roylance, Jerry W., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 30)
    - Royon, Betty, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 31)
    - Rubin, Morris H., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 32)
    - Ruiz, Jorge Martin, 1971 (Box-folder 155: 33)
    - Ruiz de la Hermosa Villegas, Elfrida, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 34)
    - Ruiz Padilla, Manuel, 1969 (Box-folder 155: 35)
    - Ruiz Sanchez, Santiago, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 36)
    - Rumsfeld, Donald, 1971 (Box-folder 155: 37)
    - Rupley, A. S., 1971 (Box-folder 155: 38)
    - Rush, Kenneth, 1971 (Box-folder 155: 39)
    - Rusk, Dean, undated (Box-folder 155: 40)
    - Russell, Sir John, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 41)
    - Rute Villanova, Carlos, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 42)
    - Ruwe, Nicholas, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 155: 43)
    - Ryan, Frank T., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 155: 44)
    - Ryan, John D., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 155: 45)
    - Ryder, Frank J., Jr., 1969 (Box-folder 155: 46)
    - Saadeddin, Omar D., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 47)
    - Sadd, Victor, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 155: 48)
    - Saenz, Hector M., 1971 (Box-folder 155: 49)
    - Saenz de Heredia, Jose Luis, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 50)
    - Safire, William, 1971 (Box-folder 155: 51)
    - Saint Innocent, Marquis of, 1969 (Box-folder 155: 52)
    - Saint Phalle, Thibaut de, 1969 (Box-folder 155: 53)
    - Salas Amaro, Alberto, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 54)
    - Salazar, Francisco, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 55)
    - Saliba, Jacob, 1969 (Box-folder 155: 56)
    - Salvador Diaz Benjumea, Julio, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 155: 57)
    - Samuels, Nathaniel, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 58)
    - Sanchez, Manolo, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 59)
    - Sanchez Bella, Alfredo, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 155: 60)
    - Sanchez Escribano Rico, Julian, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 61)
    - Sanchez Saldana, Antonio, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 62)
    - Sandlin, Marlin E., 1969 (Box-folder 155: 63)
    - Santana, Manuel, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 155: 64)
    - Santelices, Sergio, 1969 (Box-folder 155: 65)
    - Santiago de Pablo, Luis, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 66)
    - Sanza, Francisco Javier, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 155: 67)
    - Sargeant, Howland H., 1969 (Box-folder 155: 68)
    - Satrustegui, Ignacio, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 69)
    - Sauer, Walter C., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 70)
    - Saunders, Dorothy M., 1971 (Box-folder 155: 71)
    - Saunders, William K., 1971 (Box-folder 155: 72)
    - Saveskie, Peter N., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 73)
    - Sawyer, Wesley N., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 74)
    - Saxon, Daniel, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 75)
    - Sayles, Donald A., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 76)
    - Scali, John A., 1971 (Box-folder 155: 77)
    - Scanlon, Lucie, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 78)
    - Scarney, Shelley, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 155: 79)
    - Schaeffer, William Lawrence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 155: 80)
    - Schaetzel, J. Robert, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 155: 81)
    - Schedler, Spencer J., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 155: 82)
    - Schindler, Carl, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 83)
    - Schlafly, Phyllis, 1971 (Box-folder 155: 84)
    - Schmelkes, Norbert W., 1969 (Box-folder 155: 85)
    - Schmidt, Evelyn B., 1970 (Box-folder 155: 86)
    - Schnitzler, William F., 1969 (Box-folder 155: 87)
    - Schultz, Henry N., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 155: 88)
    - Schumacher, Erma, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 155: 89)
    - Schute, Norman V., 1969 (Box-folder 155: 90)
    - Scott, Hugh, 1970 (Box-folder 155: 91)
    - Scott, Winston M., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 155: 92)
    - Seaborg, Glenn T., 1970 (Box-folder 156: 1)
    - Seamans, Robert C., Jr., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 2)
    - Searles, Robert N., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 3)
    - Sears, John P., 1970 (Box-folder 156: 4)
    - Sears, Mary Helen, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 5)
    - Seely, J. Grove, 1969 (Box-folder 156: 6)
    - Seidler, W. D., 1970 (Box-folder 156: 7)
    - Selden, Armistead I., Jr., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 156: 8)
    - Selmier, Dean, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 9)
    - Serna, Jesus de la, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 10)
    - Serra, Manuel, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 11)
    - Serra, Pedro, 1971 (Box-folder 156: 12)
    - Sevilla, Luis G. de, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 156: 13)
    - Shakespeare, Frank, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 156: 14)
    - Shannon, Thomas F., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 15)
    - Shapiro, Barney, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 16)
    - Shapiro, Goodwin, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 156: 17)
    - Sharp, Joe, 1971 (Box-folder 156: 18)
    - Shaw, Robert T., 1969 (Box-folder 156: 19)
    - Shay, Patricia C., 1970 (Box-folder 156: 20)
    - Shea, Andrew B., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 156: 21)
    - Sheahan, Gerald P., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 22)
    - Sheldon, Martha, 1969 (Box-folder 156: 23)
    - Sheley, Patricia, 1971 (Box-folder 156: 24)
    - Shepard, Robert H., 1970 (Box-folder 156: 25)
    - Sherman, S., 1970 (Box-folder 156: 26)
    - Shirley, R. J., 1969 (Box-folder 156: 27)
    - Short, Frederick W., 1969 (Box-folder 156: 28)
    - Short, Hal E., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 29)
    - Sides, Andrew, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 156: 30)
    - Siegfried, Charles M., 1969 (Box-folder 156: 31)
    - Sikes, Bob, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 32)
    - Silva, J. Edward, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 33)
    - Silva, Joseph M., 1969 (Box-folder 156: 34)
    - Silva Munoz, Federico, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 156: 35)
    - Simmons, James W., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 36)
    - Simon, Lawrence E., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 37)
    - Simons, Pollard, 1971 (Box-folder 156: 38)
    - Simonsen, Robert, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 39)
    - Singleton, William H., 1970 (Box-folder 156: 40)
    - Siscoe, Frank G., 1969 (Box-folder 156: 41)
    - Sisto, John A., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 42)
    - Skeen, Arthur J., 1970 (Box-folder 156: 43)
    - Sleeper, Barbara Clark, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 44)
    - Smathers, George A., 1969 (Box-folder 156: 45)
    - Smith, Antony C., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 156: 46)
    - Smith, C. Alphonso, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 156: 47)
    - Smith, C. R., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 48)
    - Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 49)
    - Smith, Dallas, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 50)
    - Smith, David S., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 156: 51)
    - Smith, Frederick, Jr., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 156: 52)
    - Smith, H. Gerald, 1969 (Box-folder 156: 53)
    - Smith, Jack M., Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 156: 54)
    - Smith, Joseph L., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 156: 55)
    - Smith, Noel Marie, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 56)
    - Smith, Peter H., 1969 (Box-folder 156: 57)
    - Smith, Ralph T., 1970 (Box-folder 156: 58)
    - Smith, Richard Joyce, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 156: 59)
    - Smith, Winton E., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 60)
    - Snyder, E. P., Jr., 1971 (Box-folder 156: 61)
    - Snyder, Raymond E., 1969 (Box-folder 156: 62)
    - Sobrino, Lucio, 1970 (Box-folder 156: 63)